

# Aneta Falkowska

# React Developer

**4** +48 502 394 679

✓ aneta.falkowska@gmail.com





### **PROFILE**

After 14 years of work in key account management and project leadership, I decided to embrace a geeky part of my nature and transition to the world of coding. My drive to learn new things and passion for emerging technologies, combined with my newly acquired programming skills, has empowered me to create valuable solutions. During my career, I have developed a strong ability to quickly adapt to new technologies and solve challenging problems. My background in data analysis, customer service, and process improvement equips me to become a contributing team member.

# TECHNICAL & SOFT SKILLS

- JavaScript- Advanced
- HTML Advanced
- CSS Advanced
- React Intermediate
- TypeScript-Intermediate
- React Router Intermediate
- Tailwind CSS Intermediate
- Redux Beginner

- English Advanced
- Client Relations
- Cross-functional Collaboration
- Process Optimization
- Data Analysis
- Problem-Solving
- Attention to Detail
- Project Management

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### RR Donnelley:

#### Team Leader, Key Account Management

2017 - 2022

- Managed a dedicated team responsible for the comprehensive service of the Stryker account across Europe and bevond.
- · Coordinated projects related to the implementation of new products, adhering to the high standards of the automotive industry (PPAP).
- Successfully led change management initiatives for Stryker, navigating strict client regulations.
- Collaborated with client units across different regions, requiring adaptation to local needs and standards.

#### Key Accounts Project Leader

2014 - 2017

- Managed new clients onboarding, creating collaboration frameworks and ensuring smooth integration.
- Coordinated with internal teams and external partners for seamless project execution.

#### **Customer Service Specialist**

2008 - 2014

- Managed Nokia orders, ensuring high standards and coordination with European production sites.
- Developed ERP expertise, contributing to system enhancements through daily use insights.

## EDUCATION

Cracow University of Economics - International Relations Pablo de Olavide University Sevilla - Erasmus Exchange Program

2004 - 2009

2007 - 2008

#### HOBBIES

Cycling

ClimbingCooking

Reading